<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>doc@curation</title>
  <subtitle>Cloudburo Curation Product Documentation</subtitle>
  <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/</id>
  <link href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/"/>
  <link href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-06-10T09:52:17Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Felix Kuestahler</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Tutorial - Curation Publishing Workflow in 2 simple steps</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/10/tutorial-curation-publishing-workflow-in-2-simple-steps.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/10/tutorial-curation-publishing-workflow-in-2-simple-steps.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-10T09:52:17Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-10T21:52:17+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The tutorial shows the simple steps to prepare and publish a curation or self created Evernote note to your Content Site. The site identifier if the example is&lt;br&gt;
       &lt;strong&gt;sosnews&lt;/strong&gt; (replace it with your own identifier when repeating it on your own site). 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The tutorial is based on the Evernote Browers-based Client of the new generation (the distraction-free white version). For other Evernote Apps and Clients similar steps are relevant. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;Step 1: Create a note in sosnew-B-Prepare notebook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Create a note for your curation or own-created article in the sosnews 
       &lt;b&gt;-B-Prepare&lt;/b&gt; notebook. The notebook was created by the Cloudburo Curation Platform during initial setup and is your notebook for articles which are not ready yet. Theoretically you can hold such notes in any kind of notebook, but it’s quite convenient to have a dedicated one for your draft work. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/M7Gtx9XXX7Y?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Step 2: Publish the note to your Content Site&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Having completed the note, move it to the sosnews 
       &lt;b&gt;-E-CurateGen&lt;/b&gt; notebook, where it will be fetched up by the Cloudburo Curation Platform and an online article will be generated on your content site.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EGiuJyxvaLI?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The Cloudburo Curation Platform will pick periodically according to your defined scheduler the notes of the Curation Transfer Notebook, processes them, publishes them on your content site and moves the note into Notebook „sosnews 
       &lt;strong&gt;-Z-Archive&lt;/strong&gt;“. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Each note will get the tag &amp;ldquo;clb-processed&amp;rdquo; attached. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        In case you have to update an article, change the Evernote note and move it back to the sosnews- 
       &lt;b&gt;E-CurateGen&lt;/b&gt; notebook. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        That’s it, easy and straightforward. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Quick Tip - Evernote Notebook Grouping for each content site</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/10/quick-tip-evernote-notebook-grouping-for-each-content-site.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/10/quick-tip-evernote-notebook-grouping-for-each-content-site.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-10T09:42:35Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-10T21:42:37+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        In case you run multiple sites via the Cloudburo Curation Platform it’s advisable that you start using the Notebook Grouping within Evernote, to have the various site specific notebooks nicely assembled together. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/6373ef20edfba20ac6be8dcf6ce32ccf.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/7d2a8594f61e523292936c446207b749.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Feature: Customizable Evernote Publishing Schedule</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/10/feature-customizable-evernote-publishing-schedule.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/10/feature-customizable-evernote-publishing-schedule.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-10T08:38:25Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-10T20:56:55+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        The Cloudburo Content Curation Platform comes with a integrated article publishing scheduler. It allows you to define  how many news will be published 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;per day  &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;in which time window and  &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;in which time zone.&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        During the site setup step you can define the time zone where you main target content community lives, as well as on which day ( e.g. monday to friday) and in which timeframe (10:00-18:00) articles should be published. Additionally you define how many articles will be produced per hour. This feature gives you quite some flexibility to control your overall content flow.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;For example: Set your scheduler to &amp;ldquo;Monday - Friday&amp;rdquo;, from &amp;ldquo;11:00-13:00“ with 1 message per hour, in order to generate a maximum of 3 articles per day during lunch time within your time zone. &lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;For which articles will the scheduler be bypassed ?&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The scheduler for articles with the tag 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;clb-processed, &lt;/i&gt;i.e. we regenerate or update an existing article&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;clb-delete&lt;/i&gt;, i.e. we want to delete an article&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        will be skipped. These articles will be regenerated or deleted with the next Cloudburo Curation run. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Release: Beta-0.0.37</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/07/release-beta-0-0-37.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/07/release-beta-0-0-37.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-07T01:09:29Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-10T20:28:37+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        A bug fix which was introduced by 0.0.36, as well as align the CurationBot Microservice to the newest AWS Elastic Beanstalk version. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;infrastructure upgrade&lt;/b&gt;: Upgrade to &amp;ldquo;64bit Amazon Linux 2015.03 v1.4.1 running Docker 1.6.0“ (from v1.4.0)&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;bug fix 18&lt;/b&gt;: Regeneration of HTML of re-processing only pages isn’t kicked off&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Interested to participate in beta release, please register at&lt;br&gt;
       &lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Release: Beta-0.0.36</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/release-beta-0-0-36.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/release-beta-0-0-36.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-06T11:02:06Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-10T20:28:37+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        We are still in beta testing of the Cloudburo Curation Platform. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Release Date: 7.6.2015 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The Release includes the following new features or fixes 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;new feature&lt;/b&gt;: The followLink behavior got fixed and extended. Sites registered as a subdomain (automatically by us when creating a site) of curation.space will have a „nofollow“ link behavior. Sites which are using their own custom domain (configuration option, after initial creation of the site) will not have a „nofollow“ link behavior.&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;bug fix&lt;/b&gt;: clb-delete tag will be removed from the note after completing processing&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/02/feature-embed-direct-html-code-fragments.html"&gt;new feature&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/b&gt; Possibility to embed HTML code fragments, e.g. required when you want to include a sign up form from Mailchimp.&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;bug fix:&lt;/b&gt; Modified or notes tagged for deletion, will be processed independently of your current publishing schedule state. This will allow you to propagate these changes quickly and not waiting on the next free scheduler slot (which could be some hours away).&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Interested to participate in beta release, please register at&lt;br&gt;
       &lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>News Publishing Workflow in 3 simple steps</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/news-publishing-workflow-in-3-simple-steps.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/news-publishing-workflow-in-3-simple-steps.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-06T10:16:20Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-10T22:15:38+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Step 1: Working through the aggregated News in Feedly&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        This workflow starts in a news aggregation application, which allows to transfer important news articles to Evernote. My preferred application for this job is 
       &lt;a href="https://feedly.com/"&gt;feedly&lt;/a&gt; which provides One-click integration into Evernote. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The news aggregation application can be configured to listen various news channels (more on that in an own article later). For example for the site 
       &lt;a href="https://dognews.curation.space/"&gt;dognews.curation.space&lt;/a&gt; (a german news site) various news channels under the topics „DOGS“ are monitored by feedly.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/7de1be8716d3d2f74f867b0e7350859a.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The news aggregation application will present the newly published articles in an easy browse-able format. In case of feedly you may have the possibility to use optimized native applications for  your mobile devices (as for example for an iPhone or Android device). That’s important because it allows you to browse and check for news any time any where, even if you have just some minute spare time when waiting for example for the next train connection.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;The task is a quick browsing task, reading the headline and decide if the article may of importance for your news site or not&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;If not, move one and scroll down to the next article&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;If yes, open the article and transfer it to the Evernote &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;siteId&amp;gt;-A-Fetch&lt;/i&gt; notebook. The notebook was created by the Cloudburo Curation Platform and will be monitored periodically for new notes. &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;New notes will fetched by the Cloudburo Curation Platform, the source article will be fully extracted and your note updated. &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Having done that the note will be transferred to your &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;sitedId&amp;gt;-B-Prepare&lt;/i&gt; notebook, ready for the next step of the workflow&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        My experience using this workflow shows that you can easily browse through 30 news within 1-3 minutes, storing around 10% for later checking to Evernote. I do that normally in the morning when commuting to the office. Speed reading and transferring is essential because quite easily you have to check some hundred news per day depending on the monitored news channels. With feedly you can do the task on your mobile with one hand and one thumb even in a crowded public transport. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The video shows you the task (we are using the Browser base Desktop version of feedly in this example) 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lJmQ0cYjZd0?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 24px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;Step 2: Sifting through the preselected news and make them publishing ready in Evernote&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The second step for getting your news ready for publishing is, to sit down, sift through the news  which you have collected during the day(s) in Evernote and which may be important for your content site.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        As explained in step 1, you will find the stories fully extracted in plain text in your 
       &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;siteId&amp;gt;-B-Prepare&lt;/i&gt; notebook. By having the Cloudburo Curation Platform taken over the job of fetching the full content and storing it in plain text you will save considerable time in this task. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Just read the article and select the text excerpt in bold which you want take over as excerpt in your content site article. If necessary complement the text with some additional comments from your side. &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Add additional Evernote tags which will be used as content site categories&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Finally move the note to the &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;sitedId&amp;gt;-D-NewsGen&lt;/i&gt; notebook, where the note will taken over by the Cloudburo Curation Platform and an article will be generated on your online content site.&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Again a very streamlined and optimized workflow, which will take the minimum of your time and allows you to deliver fresh news to your content site in no time.&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hraAQAtrPJU?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;Step 3: Check the published article &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;on your&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt; content site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Finally do a quick online check on your content site, if the generated site is ok. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/bea9f50b2dc02639c5ed2ffa0fa659d6.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
