<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>doc@curation</title>
  <subtitle>Cloudburo Curation Product Documentation</subtitle>
  <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/</id>
  <link href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/"/>
  <link href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-06-07T01:09:29Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Felix Kuestahler</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Release: Beta-0.0.37</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/07/release-beta-0-0-37.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/07/release-beta-0-0-37.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-07T01:09:29Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-07T22:16:00+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        A bug fix which was introduced by 0.0.36, as well as align the CurationBot Microservice to the newest AWS Elastic Beanstalk version. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;infrastructure upgrade&lt;/b&gt;: Upgrade to &amp;ldquo;64bit Amazon Linux 2015.03 v1.4.1 running Docker 1.6.0“ (from v1.4.0)&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;bug fix 18&lt;/b&gt;: Regeneration of HTML of re-processing only pages isn’t kicked off&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Interested to participate in beta release, please register at&lt;br&gt;
       &lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Release: Beta-0.0.36</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/release-beta-0-0-36.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/release-beta-0-0-36.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-06T11:02:06Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-07T15:19:57+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        We are still in beta testing of the Cloudburo Curation Platform. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Release Date: 7.6.2015 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The Release includes the following new features or fixes 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;new feature&lt;/b&gt;: The followLink behavior got fixed and extended. Sites registered as a subdomain (automatically by us when creating a site) of curation.space will have a „nofollow“ link behavior. Sites which are using their own custom domain (configuration option, after initial creation of the site) will not have a „nofollow“ link behavior.&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;bug fix&lt;/b&gt;: clb-delete tag will be removed from the note after completing processing&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/02/feature-embed-direct-html-code-fragments.html"&gt;new feature&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/b&gt; Possibility to embed HTML code fragments, e.g. required when you want to include a sign up form from Mailchimp.&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;bug fix:&lt;/b&gt; Modified or notes tagged for deletion, will be processed independently of your current publishing schedule state. This will allow you to propagate these changes quickly and not waiting on the next free scheduler slot (which could be some hours away).&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Interested to participate in beta release, please register at&lt;br&gt;
       &lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html"&gt;https://cloudburo.net/docs/products.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>News Publishing Workflow in 3 simple steps</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/news-publishing-workflow-in-3-simple-steps.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/news-publishing-workflow-in-3-simple-steps.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-06T10:16:20Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-07T15:19:57+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Step 1: Working through the aggregated News in Feedly&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        This workflow starts in a news aggregation application, which allows to transfer important news articles to Evernote. My preferred application for this job is 
       &lt;a href="https://feedly.com/"&gt;feedly&lt;/a&gt; which provides One-click integration into Evernote. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The news aggregation application can be configured to listen various news channels (more on that in an own article later). For example for the site 
       &lt;a href="https://dognews.curation.space/"&gt;dognews.curation.space&lt;/a&gt; (a german news site) various news channels under the topics „DOGS“ are monitored by feedly.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/7de1be8716d3d2f74f867b0e7350859a.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The news aggregation application will present the new published articles in easy browse-able format. In case of feedly you may have the possibility to use optimized native application versions for  your mobile devices (as for example for an iPhone or Android device). That’s important because it allows you to browse and check for news any time any where, even if you have just some minute spare time when waiting for the next connection.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;The task is a quick browsing task, reading the headline and decide if the article may of importance for your news site or not&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;If not, move one and scroll down to the next article&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;If yes, open the article and transfer it to the Evernote &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;siteId&amp;gt;-A-Fetch&lt;/i&gt; notebook. The notebook was created by the Cloudburo Curation Platform and will be monitored periodically for new notes. &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;New notes will fetched by the Cloudburo Curation Platform, the source article will be fully extracted and your note updated. &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Having done that the note will be transferred to your &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;sitedId&amp;gt;-B-Prepare&lt;/i&gt; notebook, ready for the next step of the workflow&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        My experience using this workflow shows that you can easily browse through 30 news within 1-3 minutes, storing around 10% for later checking to Evernote. I do that normally in the morning when commuting to the office. Speed reading and transferring is essential because quite easily you have to check some hundred news per day depending on the monitored news channels. With feedly you can do the task on your mobile with one hand and one thumb even in a crowded public transport. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The video shows you the task (we are using the Browser base Desktop version of feedly in this example) 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lJmQ0cYjZd0?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 24px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;Step 2: Sifting through the preselected news and make them publishing ready in Evernote&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The second step for getting your news ready for publishing is, to sit down, sift through the news  which you have collected during the day(s) in Evernote and which may be important for your content site.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        As explained in step 1, you will find the stories fully extracted in plain text in your 
       &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;siteId&amp;gt;-B-Prepare&lt;/i&gt; notebook. By having the Cloudburo Curation Platform taken over the job of fetching the full content and storing it in plain text you will save considerable time in this task. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;ul&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Just read the article and select the text excerpt in bold which you want take over as excerpt in your content site article. If necessary complement the text with some additional comments from your side. &lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Add additional Evernote tags which will be used as content site categories&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Finally move the note to the &lt;i&gt;&amp;lt;sitedId&amp;gt;-D-NewsGen&lt;/i&gt; notebook, where the note will taken over by the Cloudburo Curation Platform and an article will be generated on your online content site.&lt;/li&gt; 
       &lt;li&gt;Again a very streamlined and optimized workflow, which will take the minimum of your time and allows you to deliver fresh news to your content site in no time.&lt;/li&gt; 
      &lt;/ul&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hraAQAtrPJU?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;Step 3: Check the published article &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;on your&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt; content site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 18px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Finally do a quick online check on your content site, if the generated site is ok. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/bea9f50b2dc02639c5ed2ffa0fa659d6.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Content Publishing Guidelines and Community Rules</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/content-publishing-guidelines-and-community-rules.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/content-publishing-guidelines-and-community-rules.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-06T10:16:18Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-07T15:19:57+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        Here are some common-sense rules that&amp;rsquo;ll help you steer clear of trouble. Please take these rules seriously and take them to heart. Don&amp;rsquo;t try to look for loopholes or try to lawyer your way around the guidelines—just understand them and try to respect the spirit in which they were created. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Nudity or sexual content&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Cloudburo Curation Platform is not for pornography or sexually explicit content. If this describes your content (text, image,video), even if it&amp;rsquo;s a video of yourself, don&amp;rsquo;t post it as content. Also, be advised that we work closely with law enforcement and we report child exploitation. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Violent or graphic content&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        It&amp;rsquo;s not okay to post violent or gory content that&amp;rsquo;s primarily intended to be shocking, sensational, or disrespectful. If posting graphic content in a news or documentary context, please be mindful to provide enough information to help people understand what&amp;rsquo;s going on. Don&amp;rsquo;t encourage others to commit specific acts of violence.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Hateful content&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Cloudburo Curation Platform is a platform for free expression. But we don&amp;rsquo;t support content that promotes or condones violence against individuals or groups based on race or ethnic origin, religion, disability, gender, age, nationality, veteran status, or sexual orientation/gender identity, or whose primary purpose is inciting hatred on the basis of these core characteristics. This can be a delicate balancing act, but if the primary purpose is to attack a protected group, the content crosses the line. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Spam, misleading metadata, and scams&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Everyone hates spam. Don&amp;rsquo;t create misleading descriptions, tags, titles, or thumbnails in order to increase views. It&amp;rsquo;s not okay to post large amounts of untargeted, unwanted or repetitive content, including comments and private messages. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Harmful or dangerous content&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Don&amp;rsquo;t post content  that encourage others to do things that might cause them to get badly hurt, especially kids. Content showing such harmful or dangerous acts may get removed depending on their severity. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Copyright&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Respect copyright. Only upload content that you made or that you&amp;rsquo;re authorized to use. This means don&amp;rsquo;t upload videos, images, text you didn&amp;rsquo;t make, or use content  that someone else owns the copyright to without necessary authorizations. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Threats&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Things like predatory behavior, stalking, threats, harassment, intimidation, invading privacy, revealing other people&amp;rsquo;s personal information, and inciting others to commit violent acts or to violate the Terms of Use are taken very seriously. Anyone caught doing these things may be permanently banned. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;We use to „nofollow“ link attribute for any *.curation.space site&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        In order to protect our domain curation.space, as well as any platform user from bad spam linking introduced in any Curation user site (which is obviously against the above rule and removed as soon as detected) any link in site  content of *.curation.space will be attributed as „ 
       &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nofollow"&gt;nofollow&lt;/a&gt;“. This instructs search engines the hyperlink should not influence the ranking of the link’s target in the search index. In case you use your on domain name for your Cloudburo Curation site, the nofollow attribute will not used for your content links. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;Do you think a specific curation.space content site is against the here described rules ?&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        You might not like everything you see on curation.space. Some of the content might offend you. If you think it&amp;rsquo;s inappropriate,  submit a request  for review by our Cloudburo staff (&lt;a href="mailto:info@cloudburo.net"&gt;info@cloudburo.net&lt;/a&gt;). 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        These rules were taken over and slightly adapted from the 
       &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/yt/policyandsafety/communityguidelines.html"&gt;YouTube Community Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;. 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Working with Evernote - some inspiring use cases</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/working-with-evernote-some-inspiring-use-cases.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/06/working-with-evernote-some-inspiring-use-cases.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-06T04:12:29Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-07T15:19:57+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        Evernote lets you capture and share everything that&amp;rsquo;s important to you in a single, easily accessible place. It’s building your content collection backbone for all your valuable information assets. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Out of that foundation of news and articles you now can build your online content site serving your community with your opinion and topic knowledge by integrating Evernote with the Cloudburo Curation Platform. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Starting to use Evernote in your daily life (be it in business or private) may have the power to influence, change and improve your daily workflows and laborious activities in a positive way.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        It’s worth to check out some inspiring examples how people are using Evernote. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL4I5cq2DfrSoJPvZKn-kYbBYpa_5f5wMj"&gt;Evernote’s Stories Youtube channel&lt;/a&gt; outlines such use cases of Evernote usage for optimizing and improving daily work activities. Three examples 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        In the first video ModCloth’s Senior Online Editor explains who she is tackling everyday tasks and a major redesign of their blog with Evernote.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VVh1AfGxhZA?list=PL4I5cq2DfrSoJPvZKn-kYbBYpa_5f5wMj?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Another video takes a look inside San Francisco bakery Craftsman &amp;amp; Wolves and shows how its chef, William Werner, runs his business with Evernote. For him Evernote was a „absolute game changer“ (an experience which I personally also made) 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/h8qegSP-h0w?list=PL4I5cq2DfrSoJPvZKn-kYbBYpa_5f5wMj?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        As a third example how to use Evernote for collaborating directly with your clients, refer to the following  video of Chad Williams who is running a fitness business. Instead of sending email’s and pdf’s around he uses directly Evernote for stay up-to-date with his clientele. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;div class="responsive-video"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HQ851ehn890?list=PL4I5cq2DfrSoJPvZKn-kYbBYpa_5f5wMj?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Having Evernote as your daily companion (well your mobile is normally all the times with you), it’s an easy step to integrate with Cloudburo and to reach out with your content to the online community. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        Refer to some use cases how people are using the 
       &lt;a href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/tags/showcase.html"&gt;Cloudburo Curation Platform&lt;/a&gt; as an extension to Evernote. 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Feature: Embed direct HTML code fragments</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/02/feature-embed-direct-html-code-fragments.html"/>
    <id>https://curation.cloudburo.net/2015/06/02/feature-embed-direct-html-code-fragments.html</id>
    <published>2015-06-02T06:12:53Z</published>
    <updated>2015-06-07T15:19:57+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        For certain third party tools integration, e.g. adding a signup form for your periodic 
       &lt;a href="http://kb.mailchimp.com/lists/signup-forms/add-a-signup-form-to-your-website"&gt;MailChimp&lt;/a&gt; managed newsletter to the content site, it’s necessary to embed some HTML.&lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        This can easily achieved by using the following marker elements 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/9cb41349c3a1f3beaac25ce13486b962.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        In the example below the HTML code for a MailChimp Newsletter was added 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/743854810428b037252de5deb929e769.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;
        The generated site renders your embedded code and you are ready to serve your community with a newsletter. 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img class="img-responsive img-thumbnail article" src="/images/d772d0c7f5651eed94e0007f572d980e.png" /&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;br&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt; 
      &lt;div&gt; 
       &lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt; 
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
